

Address Karachi. Pakistan

Contact +92 341 2445322 aliuzair999@gmail.com aliuzaircss@gmail.com

PROFILE

With expertise in the MERN stack, I am wellequipped to tackle any web development challenge with precision and creativity.

My career includes collaborating with various companies on a project basis, consistently transforming visions into visually stunning and highly functional applications.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022 Institute of Business Management Bachelors **HEC**

2015 - 2017 Tabani's College **HSSC BIEK**

2013 - 2015 Ghulaman-e-Abbas School SSC A KU-EB

TECHNOLOGIES

- ✓ React JS
- ✓ Next IS
- ✓ Gatsby
- ✓ Firebase
- ✓ Node IS
- ✓ Mongo DB
- ✓ Express
- ✓ Web Socket

SOFTWARE SKILLS

VS Code 00000 00000 Git 00000 Android Studio

Ali Uzair

Website

http://resume-ali.netlify.app/

Github

http://github.com/AliUzair999

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/ali-uzair

EXPERIENCE

04.2024 - present **TECHTRIFY** MERN Stack Developer

2022 - present **FREELANCING** WEB DEVELOPMENT

12.2023 - 04.2024 KDYS LAB (Pvt) Ltd React JS API Integration

10.2023 - 05.2024 **ESOUL TECHNOLOGIES** Frontend Developer

06.2023 - 08.2023 **INVISION SOLUTIONS** Frontend Developer (Internship)

2020 - 2021 **HIQAIN** Technical Project Manager

CERTIFICATION

• MERN STACK COURSE

by Expertizo University in web application development. The outline covers HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node, Express, and Mongo DB.

• WEB DEVELOPMENT

Course from SMIT in web designing and Android development. The module covers the core concepts of web and mobile application development using relevant technologies.

ENGLISH ACCESS MICROSCHOLARSHIP **PROGRAM**

by U.S Embassy Islamabad. English Language Course conducted by iEARN Pakistan.

